http://mftfence.com/privacy-notice

Settings and Links
Register
Log in
Joblist
(0)
Shopping cart
(0)
You have no items in your shopping cart.
You are running a Trial version of Nop Instant Search
Home page
ALL PRODUCTS
(562)
New Products!!!
(12)
Close Outs
(4)
New!!! Aluminum Hardware
(3)
Hinges
(72)
Latches
(33)
Drop Rods
(10)
Post Mounts
(22)
Brackets
(25)
Spring Cover
(1)
Vinyl / PVC
(80)
Vinyl Fencing Extrusions
(27)
Gate Handles
(2)
Gate Stops
(3)
GATEMASTER Gate Locks
(12)
Chain Link Fittings
(184)
Tools
(19)
Compressors
(3)
Vinyl Tools
(13)
Rhino Products
(16)
Fasteners
(18)
Miscellaneous
(38)
ALL PRODUCTS
(562)
New Products!!!
(12)
Close Outs
(4)
New!!! Aluminum Hardware
(3)
Hinges
(72)
Ornamental Embassy Hinges
(8)
Commercial and Industrial Embassy Hinges
(4)
Clamp-On Embassy Hinges
(4)
Residential Hinges
(11)
Gravity Hinges
(3)
Wall Mount Hinges
(5)
Commercial Hinges
(4)
Wrap Around Hinges
(10)
Steel Gate Frame Hinges
(2)
Galvanized Chain Link Hinges
(6)
Strap and "T" Style Hinges
(5)
Dallas Hinges
(2)
Ranch Style Agricultural Hinges
(2)
Wood Hinges
(3)
Springs
(2)
Hinge Cover (NEW)
(1)
Latches
(33)
Residential Latches
(4)
Commercial Embassy Latch
(1)
Gravity Latches
(2)
Economy Latches
(2)
Dual Lockable Latches
(6)
Double Drive Gate Bar Latches
(2)
Slide Bolt Latches
(3)
Gate Latch for Walk and Double Gates
(3)
Charleston Latches
(3)
Safety Horse Latches
(6)
Yutka Latch
(1)
Drop Rods
(10)
Residential Drop Rods
(4)
Commercial Drop Rods
(2)
Embassy Drop Rods
(1)
S.S. Drop Rods (Un-Painted)
(3)
Post Mounts
(22)
Heavy Duty Post Stiffeners
(9)
Galvanized Post Stiffeners
(2)
"X" Post Mounts
(2)
Post Mount w/Welded Plate
(2)
Galvanized Post Mount (No Wedge)
(2)
Galvanized Post Mount (With Wedge)
(3)
Vinyl Post and Rail Mount
(2)
Brackets
(25)
Spring Cover
(1)
Heavy Duty Post Stiffeners
(9)
Galvanized Bracket
(3)
S.S. Leveling Plate
(2)
Tap Root Post Anchors
(6)
Hand Rail Bracket
(2)
Trellis Bracket
(2)
Vinyl / PVC
(80)
Gothic Tops and Bases
(8)
Globe Cap
(1)
New England Tops and Skirts
(4)
Patriot Caps and Skirts
(4)
Post Skirts
(7)
Apex Caps
(9)
Spade and Pointed Caps
(4)
Dog Eared Caps
(3)
Cap Plugs
(2)
PVC End Cap
(1)
Flat Caps
(12)
Pyramid Internal Caps
(4)
Vinyl Wall Mounts
(6)
Vinyl Railing Mounts
(5)
Slide-In Rail Mounts
(2)
Gate Pockets
(4)
Screw Plugs
(1)
Clips
(2)
Ornamental Vinyl Rings
(1)
Injection Molded Arc
(1)
PVC Glue
(3)
Vinyl Fencing Extrusions
(27)
Gate Handles
(2)
Gate Stops
(3)
GATEMASTER Gate Locks
(12)
Chain Link Fittings
(184)
Aluminum Acorn Post Caps
(7)
Aluminum Dome Caps
(7)
Aluminum Loop Caps
(4)
Beveled Tension Bands
(20)
Economy Tension Bands
(5)
Heavy Tension Bands
(8)
Square Tension Bands
(6)
Beveled Brace Bands
(20)
Economy Brace Bands
(4)
Heavy Brace Bands
(7)
Square Brace Bands
(6)
Beveled Corner Brace Bands
(4)
2 & 3 Way Brace Bands
(6)
Large C Post Bands and Clamps
(2)
SR H Beam Brace Bands and Clamps
(2)
Kennel Bands and Clamps
(2)
Offset Rail Ends
(2)
End Rail Clamps
(6)
Heavy End Rail Clamps
(6)
Heavy Corner End Rail Clamps
(5)
Line Rail Clamps
(6)
Heavy Line Rail Clamps
(6)
Saddle Clamps
(1)
Steel Pipe Clamps
(5)
C Post Brackets
(3)
Round Post Brackets
(9)
Gate Clips
(2)
Fence Ties
(4)
Hog Rings
(1)
Wire Coils
(2)
5/16" Carriage Bolts
(9)
3/8" Carriage Bolts
(7)
Tools
(19)
Router Bits
(1)
Compressors
(3)
Vinyl Tools
(13)
Rhino Products
(16)
Fasteners
(18)
Miscellaneous
(38)
Privacy Policy
Thank you for choosing to be part of our community at Modern Fence Technologies. We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about our policy, or our practices with regards to your personal information, please contact us 262-642-9123.
When you visit our website www.mftfence.com, and use our services, you trust us with your personal information. We take your privacy very seriously. In this privacy notice, we describe our privacy policy. We seek to explain to you in the clearest way possible what information we collect, how we use it and what rights you have in relation to it. We hope you take sometime to read through it carefully, as it important.
This privacy policy applies to all information collected through our website and/or any related services, sales, marketing or events.
1. What Information Do We Collect?Personal information you disclose to us:
We collect personal information that you provide to us such as name, address, contact information such as phone numbers, and email addresses.
2. How Do We Use Your Information?We us personal information collected via our website for a variety of business purposes described below. We process your personal information for these purposes in reliance on our legitimate business interests, in order to enter into or perform a contract with you, with your consent, and/or for compliance with our legal obligation. We indicate the specific processing grounds we rely on next o each purpose listed below.
To send you marketing and promotional communications. We may use the personal information you send to us for our marketing purposes, if this is in accordance with your marketing preferences. You can opt-out of our marketing emails at any time by clicking “unsubscribe” in our emails or give us a call at 262-642-9123.
To send administrative information to you. We may use your personal information to send you product, service and new feature information and/or information about changes to our terms, conditions, and policies.
Fulfill and manage your orders. We may use your information to fulfill and mange your orders, payments, returns, and exchanges made through our website.
To post testimonials. We post testimonials on our website that may contain personal information. Prior to posting a testimonial, we will obtain your consent to use your name and testimonial. If you wish to update, or delete your testimonial, please contact us at 262-642-9123 and be sure to include your name, testimonial location, and contact information.
Request Feedback. We may use your information to request feedback and to contact you about your use of our website.
To protect our Website. We may use your information as part of our efforts to keep our website safe and secure (for example, for fraud monitoring and prevention).
3. Will Your Information Be Shared with Anyone?
Modern Fence Technologies will only process your data if you have given us specific consent to use your personal information in a specific purpose.
4. How Do We Keep Your Information Safe?
We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational security measures designed to protect the security of any personal information we process.
5. What are your rights?
If you would at any time like to review or change the information in your account or terminate your account, you can:Please give our office a call at 262-642-9123 to request your account be terminated. We will deactivate or delete your account and information form our active databases. However, some information may be retained in our files to prevent fraud.
6. Do California Residents Have Specific Privacy Rights?
California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared personal information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit our request in writing to us using the contact information provided below.
7. Do We Make Updates To This Policy?
We may update this privacy policy from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by and updated “revised” date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to his privacy policy, we may notify you either by prominently post a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy policy frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.
8. How Can You Contact Us About This Policy?
If you have questions or comments about this policy, you may email us at marketing@mftfence.com or by calling us at 262-642-9123
Copyright © 2020 Modern Fence Technologies. All rights reserved.
|
Website designed and hosted by Comstar.biz
